LAID-BACK CAMP SEASON 3
《搖曳露營△ (第三季)》
RIN AND NADESHIKO'S INAGAKO SPRING CAMP
(凜與撫子的伊奈湖春季露營)
MINAMI-ALPS INAGAKO FOREST PARK
(南阿爾卑斯伊奈湖森林公園)
Finally at Inagako Forest.
到伊奈湖森林了
Let's see…
我看看喔
The forest park is beyond the parking lot,
這個停車場的對面是森林營區
so the lake area is behind the rest area.
休息站的後面是湖畔營區嗎
SET MENU, FOREST SOUP CURRY, 1100 YEN
(套餐菜單 森林湯咖哩 1100圓)
Forest Soup Curry.
森林湯咖哩
Gulp.
吞口水
In any case, let's check in first.
總之 先去登記入住吧
The reception
管理處
should be over there.
好像是那裡呢
A HOLE IN A TREE IS A SHARED HOME IN THE FOREST
(樹洞是森林裡的共享公寓)
This isn't the reception.
這裡不是管理處喔
-So the reception's over there. -Reception…
-原來管理處在那邊嗎 -管理處…
Excuse me.
不好意思
One night at the lake area
我要在湖畔營區住一晚
and a bundle of firewood, please.
另外 還想買一捆柴薪
In that case,
那麼
please fill in your name and address here.
請在這裡寫下您的住家地址和名字
Rin!
小凜…
I found a secret campsite
我在南阿爾卑斯市的山裡
in the Minami-Alps!
發現一個神秘的露營場喔
A secret campsite?
神秘露營場?
I saw it on Guruguru Map.
我是在咕嚕咕嚕地圖上看到的
It's one of the lakeside camps you like,
那邊是妳喜歡的湖畔露營場
and there's an observatory deck overlooking Kofu too!
而且好像還有個觀景台 可以俯瞰甲府喔
Oh, this is Inagako.
這不是伊奈湖嗎
Rin, you know the place?
小凜 妳知道這裡嗎
I pass by that area often,
我經常騎車經過那附近
so I know there's a lake there.
所以隱約知道那邊有一座湖
Didn't know they had a campsite there, though.
不過 原來那裡是露營場啊
We've got a few days of spring break left,
反正離開學還有一點時間
want to go on one last camping trip before school starts?
要不要趁春假結束前 再去露營一次呢?
Sure, let's do it.
好啊 一起去吧
Reached Kajikazawa!
到鰍澤了
Cycling to the campsite now!
現在正騎著腳踏車朝露營場前進
It's about 10 kilometres from Kajikazawa to here.
從鰍澤到這裡大約10公里
With Nadeshiko's stamina,
以撫子的體力
she'll probably be here before noon.
應該中午前會到這裡吧
The clouds are blocking the view
現在稍微被雲遮住了
of Mt. Fuji.
看不到富士山呢
All right, one last push to Inagako!
好 再加把勁就到伊奈湖了
Everything's all set up.
裝備都搭設好了
The field area here is completely separate
這裡的草地廣場
from the camping zone.
和露營區是完全區分開來的呢
The fees are higher,
雖然價格偏高
but it isn't crowded like in the free camping sites.
但這裡就像自由露營區一樣 不用人擠人
The comfort and space are much appreciated.
反而更有開放感 讓人覺得很舒適
That's a big carp.
好大的鯉魚
Could this be
這裡
another a well-kept secret spot?
該不會是個相當隱密的秘境吧
Found a hot spring deep in the mountains!
發現一個深山裡的溫泉
A hot spring, huh?
溫泉啊
Was there a hot spring on the way here?
剛才來這裡的路上 有經過溫泉嗎
It should've been a straight path to the campsite!
應該直直走就會到露營場了啊
I don't remember it being this far!
有這麼遠嗎
GOOD JOB!
(辛苦妳了)
Takao's Diamond Fuji.
高下的鑽石富士
Is this the place Aki and the girls visited during New Year's?
這裡就是小明她們 新年時來過的地方嗎
Wait, does that mean I…
咦 也就是說 難道我…
So
所以
"CAMPSITE, TO KAJIKAZAWA, HIRABAYASHI" you missed the turn at the Hirabayashi,
(露營場 往鰍澤 平林) 妳在經過平林部落的時候忘記轉彎
"TAKAO DIAMOND FUJI" ended up riding all the way to Takao,
(高下鑽石富士) 結果一路騎到高下
and then had to cross the mountains a second time to get back here?
後來為了從那邊騎回來 整整翻過了2座山嗎
Ah,
哎呀
I guess I should check the map more often.
果然還是要適時 確認一下地圖比較好呢
This campsite is on a mountain.
這個露營場位在山上
You should have noticed something was off when you started going downhill.
當妳騎到下坡的時候 就該發現不對勁啊
It should be ready.
應該好了吧
Baked apple.
烤蘋果
I'm delicious!
很好吃唷
All sliced up.
切好了
Now just to sprinkle on some cinnamon.
接著只差撒上肉桂了
Nadeshiko, I got the ice cream.
撫子 我買冰回來囉
Thanks, Rin.
謝謝妳 小凜
Managed to buy them before the rest area closed.
趕在休息區下班前買到了
Thank goodness.
太好了
Finally, top it off with the ice cream…
最後再放上冰淇淋
And the sweet apple tortilla…
烤蘋果甜口味墨西哥薄餅
is done!
完成
That is way too much ice cream.
不是 妳的冰也放太多了吧
Time to dig in!
我要開動了
See, it's hard to bite into now, isn't it?
妳看 這不是變得很難咬嗎
Tastes so good.
好吃
It really does.
真的很好吃呢
The chicken tortilla we had earlier was great,
雖然剛才吃的 雞肉墨西哥薄餅也很讚
but this dessert version is just as nice.
但甜口味的也很不錯呢
Right?
對吧
I've always thought tortillas are the perfect camping food
我一直覺得墨西哥薄餅跟露營很搭
since you just wrap them up and eat them.
畢竟只要捲起來就好
And it cuts down on the washing up.
也能減少要洗的東西
It could be fun to prepare different fillings
團體露營的時候
and have everyone wrap their own
或許也能準備各種料理
during a group camp.
包在這裡面吃呢
That sounds like a great idea.
感覺不錯耶
Spread cream cheese,
先塗奶油起司
add kiwi slices,
再放上奇異果
drizzle mango sauce, and top it off with fresh cream! Yum!
並淋上芒果醬和生奶油的吃法 也很不錯喔
There really isn't one, is there?
果然沒有嗎
What's up?
怎麼了嗎
I was looking for campsites
我剛才找了一下高下附近
near Takao.
有沒有露營場
If there was one,
原本想說如果有
we could see Diamond Fuji during a New Year camp.
跨年露營的時候就能看到鑽石富士了
There are new campsites popping up everywhere.
現在各地都蓋了新的露營場
It'd be great if one could be built there.
要是那邊也能蓋一座就好了
Yeah.
就是說啊
The scenery is beautiful there.
畢竟那邊風景很漂亮
If they had a campsite, it would definitely be popular.
如果有露營場 應該會很受歡迎吧
But I imagine the battle for bookings
不過感覺年初年末的時候 都會引發一場預約爭奪戰
would be intense around New Year's and the holidays.
因為大家都想看鑽石富士
That's very possible.
有可能呢
If a campsite were built there,
如果那邊能蓋露營場
I'd love for the camping area to be on a grassy field.
我希望營區可以在草地上
A quiet spot where I could enjoy solo camping
要是能有個可以安靜地 享受單人露營的營區
would make me really happy.
我會很開心的
Sounds amazing.
感覺很棒耶
Also, I wouldn't mind if there wasn't a shop,
還有 沒有販賣部沒關係
but I'd hope they at least sold firewood.
但希望能有個賣柴薪的地方
And it'd be great if they allowed pets
最好還能開放寵物入住
so people could bring their dogs along for camping.
讓狗狗們一起來露營
Then Chikuwa could join us too.
這樣竹輪就能一起來了呢
Rin,
小凜
let's go see Diamond Fuji next year!
明年我們也去看鑽石富士吧
Sure,
嗯
if I don't forget.
如果有記得的話